rimweb.in 2008-12-21

# RIMweb.in :: Reliance Mobile ( Reliance IndiaMobile ) Discussion Forums

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to RIMweb.in. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used.

## Registration

Some basic personal information is required in order to register with RIMweb.in:

  * **Name** \- Your first and last name help us to personalize your online experience. For example, your "My Forums" list of favorite online communities may feature your first and/or last name
  * **Email Address** \- By providing your email address, you can receive important messages via your existing email account. Message board notifications, personalized newsletters, and messages sent to you by other RIMweb.in members rely on the email address you provide when you register
  * **User Name** \- This is how you are identified when you participate in forums. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed

## Information RIMweb.in Requests

When you register, you are asked to give demographic information (like birth year, occupation, and gender). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. This information can also be used to provide you with content that may be of interest to you, and to show you advertisements that are relevant to your demographic information. RIMweb.in uses outside ad companies to display ads on its sites. These ads may contain cookies. While RIMweb.in uses cookies in other parts of its sites, the ad companies also use cookies with the ads displayed, and RIMweb.in may not have access to this information.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

No children under 13 are allowed to participate in RIMweb.in

## Participation

The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join RIMweb.in, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that RIMweb.in obtains this information when you login to your account and use the service. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on RIMweb.in to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, RIMweb.in checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the RIMweb.in login screen, where you can quickly and easily login to your account, or signup for RIMweb.in if you are not yet a member. Cookies are also used in conjunction with some ad banners to determine their effectiveness.

## Cookies

RIMweb.in uses cookies to customize your experience while using the Forums. A cookie is a small text file that many Web sites write through your browser when you visit them. A cookie can only be read by the site that places it, so RIMweb.in can't "see where you've been" based on any other cookies in your browser. Cookies are generally supported in version 3.0 and newer of Internet Explorer, 2.02 and newer of Netscape, and 3.0 and newer of AOL. Netscape Navigator uses a single file called "cookies.txt" to record all cookies, and you can open this file in any text editor to see what it looks like. On a Macintosh computer, the Netscape cookie file is called "MagicCookie". Internet Explorer uses a separate file for each cookie, which typically reside in "C:\Windows\Profiles\User\Cookies." Most browsers also allow the option of displaying a warning before accepting a cookie, or refusing all cookies. Declining cookies while participating in forums may result in some of features not working properly.

## Private Messages

The purpose of private messages is to allow for discreet conversations between members. Normal forums rules apply to private messages.

If you receive a private message which breaches RIMweb.in forums guidelines, is threatening, abusive or contains illegal content please forward it onto one of the RIMweb.in administrators immediately. Do not reply to the person sending you the private message.

While the name "private messages" gives the suggestion that they are private, they are part of the database & as such accessible to RIMweb.in administrators.

So, while they are private, they are not necessarily secret. RIMweb.in has a policy of respecting member's privacy & would never access member's private message unless the following reasons applied:

  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to engage in illegal behaviour
  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to slander a person or business, which could result in damage to their reputation
  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to cause harm to others
  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to solicit money from members, such as phishing
  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to spam members
  * We have reason to believe that a member is using the PM system to threaten members
  * We believe that a person is using the PM system in order to cause damage to RIMweb.in
  * We believe that a person is using the PM system for any electronic piracy related activities

## RIMweb.in emails/newsletters

As a registered user, you may receive informational email messages from RIMweb.in from time to time. All registered members are required to receive such communications. If you wish to stop these emails, you may terminate your membership at any time.

## Public Forums

RIMweb.in hosts message boards, chat and other services for both public and private forums. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public forums becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

RIMweb.in site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. RIMweb.in' servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.

## Termination

You can elect to terminate your membership with RIMweb.in at any time. Simply send an email to forums [at] RIMweb.in with the subject "Account Termination Request" and mention your username and password in the email body. Upon termination, your account information will not necessarily be removed entirely from RIMweb.in - this is to reserve your identity so that no one else can create a new account with your membername or email address, and also allows you the privilege of reactivating your account at a later date if you wish to use RIMweb.in again. The termination of your RIMweb.in membership will not automatically terminate any affiliated memberships or registrations you have formed through RIMweb.in.

## Summary

In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, RIMweb.in appreciates the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care.
